# Maciej Dabrowski



maciejdabrowski99@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/dabrowski-maciej



+48669851696



https://maciekdabrowski.github.io/

#### Summary

Process-oriented data analyst, with proven skill driving process and data integrity improvements. Attentive to sales data, experienced in interpreting and analyzing data to drive growth for a global corporation. Fluent in English and Polish, with an intermediate understanding of German.

### **Experience**

#### iff Data Analyst

**IFF** 

Feb 2022 - Jan 2023 (1 year)

- Performing quantitative and qualitative analysis to support data-driven projects
- · Maintaining and cleaning up master data for optimal data analysis using Excel and SQL
- · Coordinating, supporting, and helping the project team to resolve issues with master data, reporting, and commercial systems integration
- · Analyzing master data in SAP, SFDC (Salesforce), and other enterprise systems to identify opportunities for procedure alignment, data harmonization, and process improvements
- · Working with the master data team to recommend enhancements to existing procedures, incorporating user feedback to address information gaps
- · Assisting in the development, improvement and documentation of master data governance framework with a focus on improving data quality for data-driven business analytics

#### **Digital Marketing Intern**

40Love.ai

Jul 2019 - Dec 2019 (6 months)

- · Creating and keeping customers through social media marketing, SEO, content marketing, and paid advertising
- · In charge of ad campaigns on Facebook Ads and Google Ads
- · Extensively used Google Analytics to find a target audience and analyze insights from website traffic
- Helped with generating sales via direct messaging

#### **Education**



#### King's College London

BSc, Economics and Management

2018 - 2021

Pursued a three-year course of study in Economics and Management, laying groundwork for eventual career in Business Analytics.

Core Modules: Digital Marketing, International Marketing, Sales and Marketing, Technology Strategy, Crafting Entrepreneurial Opportunities, Leadership: Theory and Practice, Marketing Strategy and Planning, Communication in Organisations.

## University of Vienna

Bachelor of Science - BS, International Business Administration 2019 - 2020

Awarded a place at the University of Vienna to undertake a year-long Erasmus+ Exchange Programme.

Core Modules: Marketing, Strategy, Econometrics, Decision and Game Theory, Microeconomics, Macroeconomics, Corporate Finance, Organization of the International Firm, Ethics of Artificial Intelligence

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

- Enterprise Course SGH Warsaw School of Economics
- in Google Analytics Essential Training LinkedIn
- Data Analytics Course Le Wagon
- Google Data Analytics Certificate Coursera

#### **Skills**

Databases • Database Management System (DBMS) • Salesforce.com • SQL • Power BI • Python • Tableau • Extract, Transform, Load (ETL) • Microsoft Excel • Digital Marketing